Presented by NEW
A Sanai Pictures Production
Co-produced by Film Train
Executive Producer KIM Woo-taek
HWANG Jung-min
HAN Hye-jin
Directed by HAN Dong-wook
MAN IN LOVE
Oh Lord,
despite all the hardships of life,
in our days of bad economy,
Your flock is grateful to You,
and we will continue to
give our offerings to You.
Your business is booming,
why do you need a loan?
A large congregation
doesn't equal big money.
And this ain't no business!
It's a holy place of worship.
Like hell...
This loan isn't
authorized by the office.
It's a private loan from me, here.
Thanks, Tae-il.
I seriously will pray for you.
Forget it, pray for yourself,
to quit gambling.
I pray everyday!
You'll go to hell at this rate.
Mr. HAN!
Let's win for our Lord!
Whatever, man.
Because of redevelopment,
all the neighbors fled,
My kids' education fee's rising,
I don't know what to do!
Goddammit!
Why always the gloom?!
How many weeks has it been?
Everyone has a sob story,
shall I end things here?!
- Mr. HAN!
- Shut it!
Wait, that's gasoline!
Fuck this life, let's
just die together.
Mr. HAN! What's with you?!
Don't drink that!
Let go!
Back the fuck off!
My gosh...
Please don't...
Drink.
- Please, Mr. HAN.
- Drink it!
- I'm sorry!
- Just drink it!
- It's all my fault!
- Drink it, dammit!
Mr. HAN! Please stop!
Wait, please...
It's all my fault...
It's my shop rent
and kids' tuition.
I'll get the rest somehow,
I'm so sorry.
For your kids!
Gotta educate them!
Shut it!
So fucking loud!
I'm back, shithead!
Afternoon.
Yeah, speak.
40 a piece.
Fuckwad, why is it so
hard getting a seal?!
It's from the market.
Come back?!
Stay the fuck there, asshole!
Tae-il, go take care of it,
Gunsan Hospital.
Fucking morons.
When your boss speaks, at
least pretend to listen.
Good?
Yeah.
Here, take a cab.
I'm sorry, sir.
Are you new at this?
- Where?
- #824.
My father needs a
bath, please leave.
- In a coma?
- Yes.
Mister, please get up.
Could you wake up?
Missy, can we talk?
If you don't feel chatty,
take a look at this.
Isn't this illegal?
Illegal? Is that why
he took a loan from us?
Be quiet, we're in a hospital.
I'll need to talk to him directly.
- Bring him outside.
- Yes, sir.
- Out of the way.
- What are you doing?!
- Fuck off!
- Don't touch him!
- Fucking bitch!
- Get out!
Goddammit!
Fuck off!
Stop fooling around,
hurry the fuck up!
Fuck off!
Don't!
Please!
- Let go!
- Fine!
I'll sign it!
I'll do it!
JU Ho-jung
You are now legally bound
to 49% monthly interest.
It includes principal
and unpaid interest.
Is that okay?
Do you have a lover?
If you do, end it soon.
No more love life for you.
Your body is not yours alone now.
It's a stressful period,
but don't get fat.
Even bar girls need to meet
certain standards too.
We are Daesan Industries.
Yes, boss.
It's done.
We'll head back to the office now.
Here!
- That's $3,000.
- Thanks, honey.
Why do you need new loan?
Bag! Bag!
For a new Chanel.
Crazy bitch...
Come by later,
I'll show it to you.
Here you go.
Amount due: $4,105
Vehicle Repossessed
- JU Ho-jung
Thank you, please come again.
Suhyup Bank
- Good night.
- Take care!
Hey!
Doesn't the bank close at 5?
Why do you get off so late?
Got a sec?
Let's grab a drink,
we need to talk.
The deadline's not up yet.
And why should I drink with you?
If you need to talk,
we can talk here.
Here?
I'm sure your colleagues
will get a kick out of it.
If you had a sob story, you
shoulda said something.
You can't just sign
everything over.
How'll that help?
How many kidneys you got?
Two, right?
Humans can live fine
with just one.
Know why we got two?
Organ transplant.
To give it to those without one.
Is this a threat?
I don't believe this...
Are we living in the middle ages?
I'll pay back in time,
so don't come to me!
I'll pay it back!
No need to raise your voice.
I'll pay!
I'll meet the deadline!
Be quiet, goddammit!
This is bullshit...
Bullshit?
Reek of alcohol!
Uncle! Wake up!
Wake the fuck up!
Come on, wake up!
How much did you have to drink?
Can't you see I'm sleeping?!
Give me some money for school!
It's for class prep!
You took some yesterday, you
don't even fucking study!
Seriously, people'll think
I'm ripping you off.
Don't be a cheapskate!
I'll pay you back!
I swear!
Do you even get meals?
Don't stay out too late!
Come home early!
What the hell do you even do?
Stop nagging me, I'm 40 years old!
Watch your tone!
I'm just worried!
Pull over at that hospital there.
This isn't a cab!
Are you sick?
Open the damn door!
Bill reminder, last notice...
What a headache...
Why're there so many bills?
Hey!
Do you speak Korean?
I told you already,
I'll pay it back!
You misunderstood me last time.
I just wanted to
give you an advice.
I'm not very good with words.
If you have a kidney transplant...
Must I spell it out for you?
I don't need your help!
You don't?
Let's be honest.
Can you really pay back?
You got bills to your neck.
Why is that your business?
So what will you do?
What do you want from me!
Keep it down.
Mister, go back inside.
- Afternoon, sir.
- Welcome back.
Back? Good work.
Northern districts.
How's the market district?
Since you're on a roll, hit it up.
Merchants are loaded these days.
They keep money under the carpet.
Major cash hoarders.
- Doo-chul!
- Yeah?
Are we friends?
Nope.
We're... a boss
and an employee.
Loan Contract
- VIP JU Ho-jung
Boss, hand this over
as Thanksgiving bonus.
Got an obsession?
Is she any different 'cause
she went to college?
Not everything,
I want the principal.
Deal?
When do you get off work?
# 65 please!
Will you stop it?!
# 66 please!
So what time do you get off?
This is workplace, you
can't hassle me here!
Please leave!
Ms. JU?
Everything okay?
Please leave your
personal life at home.
Buddy!
Wanna die?!
You wanna get arrested?
It's your fault, miss.
I know what's going on.
Obstructing your work?
Yes.
But you're doing that now.
What?
You borrowed money, right?
Didn't pay back?
Why're you bringing that up?
It's not a crime to
remind you to pay.
And I'm told he only spoke.
Have a gum, sir.
Shut it!
Just leave.
We're busy people, missy.
And you!
- You're on probation, right?
- Yes, sir.
- Be careful.
- Okay.
You need a guardian to
leave, so call your bro.
Already notified.
Uncle!
Song!
What brings you here?
So embarrassing!
Can't you stay away from here?
I'm sensitive these days.
Sensitive my ass, you mean bitchy.
It's the exam period,
it's so friggin' tough.
I got a tough business too.
Business my ass, you
mean a bitch problem.
Hey!
Let's talk another day.
Song! How about
deep fried chicken?
No, mom said to drag you home.
Drag me.
- Mom, I'm home.
- Hey.
Have dinner.
Shit, fix the damn light!
That bastard, it's
like we don't exist.
Moron, have dinner!
He doesn't wanna eat?
Dunno, he's busy with business.
Business of breaking laws?
You're single-handedly
tainting our family name!
Heard you went to the station!
Dad, shut up!
Shut up?! How could you
say that to your father?!
- Let's just eat!
- I am eating!
Just eat!
He's nothing but trouble, dad.
You're no better, act your age.
Father, we're sorry.
Private Loan Contract
Memorandum
Once the overdue bills are paid,
we can give him painkillers
and vitamin shots.
I'm sorry, it's the hospital rule.
Did you eat?
Chicken's the best
snack, let's talk.
Look here.
This is the contract you signed.
And this memo voids this contract.
See these boxes?
For every hour we meet once a
day, I'll color these boxes.
When it's all filled in,
this becomes yours.
Do you understand?
Leave if you're done.
Think it over and call me.
Call me regardless.
Daesan Industries
HAN Tae-il
So what do I have to do?
What are the conditions?
Condition?
That's...
What do you think?
We take... walks...
Walk? Then what?
And have chats...
Yo, how old are you?
We're not senile seniors.
Does it make sense to deduct
the interest for chitchats?
Forget it.
Wait...
Dammit...
Not washing up?
Give me a light.
- Yo!
- What?
Do you love me?
Love? Can't you see
I'm working?
If you don't, how
can you just strip?
And you do this for love?
What's with you?
Something wrong?
Wash up, I gotta leave soon.
I'm off.
What a waste of a shower!
Let me ask you one thing.
If I keep thinking about
you, isn't that love?
You think about me?
Just don't.
- I don't think of you.
- Shut your hole.
Does today still count?
Let's try again.
- Walk.
- And?
Have meals and drink sometimes.
And some other stuff too.
What could that be?
Mister.
Do you like me?
Or is this a new way
of threatening?
Anyways, keep your promise.
I'm off.
Got 7 colors,
I'll draw you rainbows.
I'm here.
What brings you here so early?
Had breakfast?
Nah.
I ordered some noodles, have that.
I'm busy.
But you still gotta eat.
I'll give you this chicken,
take it with you.
- Good work, I'm off.
- Take this with you!
- I didn't order...
- See you.
Ma'am...
Well, this is new.
Look here.
How is it? Nice?
You got a nice face,
but the thing is...
your style is...
menacing?
Hostile... or something...
I'm trying to say,
you got a bad taste.
And you?!
Aren't you coming?
flip the other way.
You still got it,
good for a son or two.
Stamp your seal or thumbprint.
Give me your ID.
Somethings up, paying
attention to style.
Got a girl?
Listen to yourself,
cut the bullshit.
Make it look like a million bucks.
Yeah.
Yeah, not the front one,
the back one.
Ask him!
We have a deal!
Fuck off!
Please stop!
Ask Mr. HAN!
- He gave me a week!
- Shut the hell up!
Goddammit!
Get Mr. HAN down here!
Fuck!
- Mr. HAN, buddy!
- Stay back.
You gave me a week!
Stay back, go inside.
- Wait.
- Go inside.
- This is wrong!
- I said go inside!
Go inside!
Now!
Go away!
It's over.
Come.
I told you I'd take
care of the market!
Is that how you're
taking care of the biz?
Then you shoulda said so!
Is your sweet 16 coming up?
Following a girl around?
If you're a deputy, act like...
Goddammit!
I'll take care of it.
Fine, do it your way.
Your boyfriend...
took the patient to the roof.
The protege of Pegasus?
You can't even fight
back, you're pathetic...
Hey.
I like this the best.
What are you doing?
Reading to him, so he
doesn't get bored.
Did I ask you to do this?!
Hey!
Dammit!
What's with you?
Don't ever come back,
or call me either.
What's wrong?
Is this a joke?
Is this fun to you?
What about you then?
Why are you doing this to me?
Tell me why!
I love you.
I'll pay it back,
don't ever come back.
We're not done,
I'll come down soon.
It's only been 10 minutes.
What?
Hey, honey! Honey!
What the hell?!
Why are you here?!
- Who are you?
- Get out!
- Stop that!
Let go!
I'm her brother, get the hell out!
What're you doing?!
Are your nuts?!
What now?
I love you.
What's the deal?
Can't you see I'm working?
I said I love you, let's fuck!
Strip, bitch!
I'm working!
Fuck! I said I love you!
You got no right to ignore me.
It was so hard finding that comic!
I searched so many
comic book shops.
What? Comics?
You're fucking nuts!
Let go!
Do you feel nothing when
I pour my heart out?
Do you know what love is?
At least this isn't it.
I'll pay the interest,
so don't call me anymore.
We need to monitor further,
but it looks grim.
So damn many...
Missy!
I don't joke around
with stuff like this,
I don't love you.
I take back what I said yesterday!
Daesan Industries
- Have a good meal.
- Welcome back.
- Would you like some?
- No, no.
- Ms. LEE?
- Yes?
That hospital case...
where's Mr. JU's contract?
That's... Mr. HAN...
Mr. HAN took that
as Thanksgiving bonus.
Why?
Nothing, sir.
Buddy!
Why're you looking for it?
I got a call that
Mr. JU passed away.
For deed of arrangement...
I didn't know you took care of it.
Have you eaten?
Why so late?
Get over here.
Set it up.
No, I wasn't talking to you.
Yeah, Semankum Funeral Home.
Okay.
Yup.
Mr. HAN, who passed away?
Is the shop in order?
I'm sorry about that.
If it wasn't for you I
could've shut down for good.
I'm the one thankful.
So who passed away?
Let's just go, all the
merchants are here.
- Mr. HAN!
- Look who's here!
- Whose funeral is this?
- A close relative.
Go on, all of you.
Pay your respect.
Thank you for coming,
please stay for a meal.
So hard trying to stay up.
It was easy when I gambled.
This? I said
I was the son-in-law.
Go take a nap, I'll hold the fort.
Don't like ducks?
Go somewhere else?
Go on, eat.
Take 1 ginseng, and 2 vitamins.
We got 10 more minutes.
Wanna talk?
Do you pity me?
Pity you?
What the shit...
Then do you like me?
Like you?
What the hell...
Why do you like me?
- What?
- Hurry!
I gotta get back soon!
Are you nuts?!
Stop that!
Just stay still.
You smell nice.
New perfume?
It smells so new.
You're nuts!
Absolutely nuts!
You're insane!
For real!
It's not it?
I thought you wanted this.
2 years later
# 1214 HAN Tae-il.
In accordance to Criminal
Procedure Code #471,
we stay your sentence.
- Good morning.
- Yeah.
What the hell?
Isn't this HAN Tae-il?
When did he get here?
He came last night.
Hey! Wake up!
Morning.
How did you get out?
What's wrong with your bro?
Should've told you where
he was moving to.
Finish your meal, and
sign here and here.
Finish your meal, no rush.
HAN Tae-il
Gunsan Police Station.
His new address.
You might not be the
reason for the move.
- Thank you.
- Go on.
Sir!
I was a model prisoner.
Mom, I'm not a kid anymore.
Our family has trust issue!
Song.
Uncle!
Look at this, isn't
the uniform pretty?
So different from middle school.
Our baby's all grown up,
you're a woman now.
When did you get out?
Don't you have 1 more year?
You neglected chores to
count down his sentence?
If you moved, you
should've let me know.
You sound like we purposely
moved because of you.
Why were you at the station?
What did you do?
Stop it already!
Get down and eat.
I'll eat, but not his bullshit!
How did you get out?
Did you escape?
I was released
as a model prisoner!
So full of shit...
You were a model
human being in jail?
Expect me to believe that?!
Sir, show me your ID.
Wait.
We're having a chat as a family,
why do you want his ID?
Were you listening in illegally?!
He... was released
as a model prisoner!
Sit down!
Your ID.
Dammit...
You're good.
So fast for an old man.
- Father!
- Grandpa!
Take him home.
Keep an eye on him.
Dad!
You idiot!
You got arrested again?!
You call yourself his brother?
- Let's go, dad.
- Grandpa...
Take care.
I dunno who's in trouble.
Let's just go, come on now.
Thank you officer.
How often does he do this?
Now and again.
He's fine when he comes to.
You're the blissful one, dipshit.
How could you let him
continue to drive the bus?
The funny thing is, he
doesn't forget his route.
Just focus on your own life.
Buddy,
focus on the matter at hand!
Are you his son?
What about you then?
This is the best you
can do as his son?
Perhaps you should take
him to jail with you.
You model bastard!
Goddammit!
Piss off!
You fucking pig.
How dare you!
You red-ass monkey!
- Tae-il! Honey!
- Son of bitch!
- Stop right there!
- Stop fighting!
Ho-jung.
How did you find me?
Here...
Do you not even feel sorry?
I wish you'd kill yourself.
Why are you doing this?!
Warden, I'm not leaving!
I'll never leave!
Everyone's itching to leave here!
You can't stay anymore,
that's the law!
It's a done deal.
You got maybe 3 months to live.
Get some professional treatment,
and get your affairs in order.
2 years ago
Watcha doing?
We got a laundry machine for that.
I'm done.
Sweetie!
Let's hike up that mountain.
Hike? Walking up here is a hike.
Here!
Come on, let's go.
Damn...
Holy cow...
Love ya, shit!
I wish you didn't
associate with them.
And maybe get a new job too.
Fine, no need for this again.
Honey, how about a chicken shop?
Chicken shop?
You like chicken the best.
I wish everything was chicken.
What if we go down under
'cause you eat everything?
Sweetie.
Should we have a kid?
$3-400,000 circulate
in one night.
Clientele list is complete.
She wants to play again?
She's got spidey senses.
Come to meeting on time,
look at the time!
We got a killer job,
come sit down.
Doo-chul.
I want to quit.
Take 5, go have a smoke.
I hear you loud and clear, but
how'll you make a living?
You don't even have a saving.
You need money to start anew.
This is a good gig, walk
away with a fortune.
Doo-chul!
One last big score,
and we both retire.
She put you up to this?
Goddammit...
Then whys it so fucking
hard to take an easy job?!
I'm off.
Buddy!
What about the loans
you gave privately?
You always have it your way.
So free, aren't ya?
I'll sort all the loans, so
don't lose sleep over it.
Please!
I need more time!
1 week!
Just give me 1 week!
Lord created this world in a week!
That's for the Lord!
Please don't!
Mr. HAN, not that!
Mr. HAN! Mr. HAN!
Nothing's in there!
Open it, now!
- Please...
- Open it!
Open!
Biopsy for what?
I just fainted.
What?
Are you sure?!
As you see here,
cerebrum and frontal
lobe are white.
It's a small tumor.
- If it's malignant...
- Will I die?
You have to be
open to treatments...
Is it expensive?
You'll need both radiation
and chemo-therapies.
I want a straight answer!
So how much will it cost?!
Hey, you're home?
Sweetie, here.
Dad's insurance
and I saved some up.
We can start a good chicken shop.
Then we'll get married,
and have a beautiful child.
Yeah, let's eat.
I love ya.
Shit.
Come on, eat.
So dang expensive.
Not even that good.
We can deliver, we
don't need a big shop.
Let's look around more.
Didn't you come out
during lunch break?
Yup.
I'll call after work.
Go straight home.
Okay.
Don't wander off.
I got it, get back to work.
I'm off.
There's nothing else?
Honestly, not at that budget.
You've seen it all.
Maybe in the outskirts.
But you should really start
the business in a good spot.
You liked the shop we saw, right?
No, there'll be something better.
Let's sign that place.
It's okay, we can start small.
Ho-jung.
Wasn't it difficult?
When your father was sick.
Don't even mention it.
You gave me more stress.
But it felt as though
he left me with you.
Good to see you.
Been a while, you doing okay?
It's for the last time,
living like a dog.
30 grand.
Doo-chul, if this goes wrong...
You know me, I'm better
with big scores.
And would I ask you to
hop on a sinking ship?
This is totally different.
We just march head on.
Boss.
We got a situation.
Can't you see we're talking?
Something important?
Take this money.
Sorry, gotta take care of this.
Let's talk again later.
Have some food.
Honey, we sign today,
don't be late.
I'll see you later.
This is huge.
I don't need your money.
But we're friends, consider
this your severance.
Trust me, and back me up.
I'll give you 4, no,
5 times the amount.
Please don't be late
We'll start soon,
please take your seat.
We'll now start.
Card for player, card for banker.
Player, natural 8.
Banker, natural 9.
Banker wins.
We'll start.
Card for...
The last tenant hitted big,
you'll do really well.
Evening sir, come in.
Hello.
This is the signee.
Good evening.
This is the owner.
Banker natural 9, banker wins.
Draw 6, max 8.
Ho-jung
Draw 5, max 9, banker wins.
Is she serious about this?
Just a bit longer.
Exchange booth!
Stop them!
Doo-chul! Doo-chul!
Doo-chul!
Let's go! Go now!
Let go!
Goddamn shit!
Son of a bitch!
Let go!
Motherfucker!
Go!
- No deal.
- Sir!
Sir, please wait!
- Forget it!
Sir, please hear me out.
He'll be here very soon.
Sir!
Got nothing to say?
Make an excuse.
Explain where you were,
why you couldn't come,
and about your face.
Do you know what the realtor said?
Ambitions should
match your abilities.
Gangsters can't lead
a normal life.
You promised me, you
said you won't see them!
Just stop, I feel bad enough.
Why did you do it?!
Stop it, goddammit!
Don't you know who I am?!
I'm much worse than this!
Fuck, I think you're mistaken.
Did you think I'd marry you?!
Goddamn bitch...
'You promised me.'
- 'Why did you do it?'
- Let's go home.
Let's go.
Bitches nowadays are tough.
Ma'am, check please!
Fucking motherfucker!
That fuck!
Let him be.
Dumbass bitch!
He's fucking insane!
God-fucking-damn!
Son of a bitch!
Motherfucker!
What did I fucking do?!
Go fuck yourselves!
Motherfucker!
Defendant HAN Tae-il.
For violent assaults, you
are sentenced to 3 years.
Probation Agreement
- HAN Tae-il
How long will you
keep it to yourself?
They don't need to know.
Treatment?
Getting treatment is part
of your release condition.
Sir.
Have you heard of
Doo-chul's whereabouts?
Why?
Just say hello,
don't ca use trouble.
You need to sort out your life.
Buan Industrial Refrigeration
Afternoon, boss.
Hey.
JANG Doo-chul!
- Did you count the pollacks?
- Yes, it's done.
- Correct number?
- Yes.
- Count it again.
- Yes, sir.
Everything has changed.
I see that.
Doo-chul, I want my money.
It's not like you,
digging up old grudges.
Just give me my fucking money.
You've changed too.
Probably ready to die.
You look busy,
I'll see you tonight.
You got my number.
Tae-il!
Don't come back.
Awkwardness is okay,
but not burden.
What's going on?!
- I'm sorry, boss.
- What is it!
- I'm sorry.
- What's this stench?
Let go, let go.
Fuck off!
Let go.
Got a smoke?
I lost 'em while shitting,
just have my lighter.
Dammit...
What the fuck did you do?
You messed him up?
Lift your head, fucker!
I never liked this
gold-toothed bastard.
Doo-chul, isn't this
what you wanted?
I told you,
everything has changed.
Chilly?
We've grown old.
Tae-il, don't come back.
I don't want to
feel sorry for you.
Go have a hot soup.
Doo-chul...
I'm dying...
Goddammit!
That's my head.
The white spot is a tumor.
I was gonna die in the joint,
but they won't let me.
I got nothing left to lose.
Doo-chul.
How'd you feel when I die?
My friend, it's my last favor.
I'll never resent you,
just give me my money.
JU Ho-jung!
Here.
Back at it again?
Expect me to take
this dirty money?
I don't need you,
or this, so piss off!
Ho-jung.
Honey
Do you know how I feel everyday?
And what about my life then?
JU Ho-jung!
Honey, you have to
take this, please!
You have to take this!
- Let me go!
- Please!
Let go!
Let me go!
Don't touch me!
Let go!
Please...
One moment, just one moment...
Just a little...
Please...
And 10.
- 11
- What's that?
Damn, I lost count!
What is that?!
I'm not deaf, be quiet!
What the hell are you doing?!
The outer layer was so crisp.
You can't make that at home.
Why're you all worked up again?
Look at that hand,
did you fight again?
I'm broke, can't bail
you out this time.
What's with you?!
Fuck!
Have you gone mad?!
Asshole!
Stop it!
Tae-il, are you nuts?!
What the fuck?!
What's dad doing?
Did you force him to work?!
Assfucker, because I'm so greedy!
Have you ever helped
out the family once?!
Fucking asshole!
Uncle!
Hit me!
Ungrateful bastards!
How dare you!
No better than dogs.
Goddammit!
Seriously...
I'm sick and tired of this...
Right there.
Lift your head.
Where you going?
I'm gonna give the
ointment to Tae-il.
Don't go!
Are you worried about him?
Of course, he's your brother.
Don't go!
Stay put,
I'll give it to Song then.
Don't go! Sit!
What's with you?
When Tae-il got beat up
on his high school trip.
Yeah?
You left ointment on
our front door, right?
You saw?
What?
Hey!
Rub his asshole with it!
Rub it nice and kiss it too!
Goddammit!
Ouch...
Uncovering the truth
after 20 years.
Ow that hurts...
The doctor said, using
fingers help with memory.
Dad managed to find
the box folding gig.
Grandpa's not so bad
because of dad's efforts,
we praised him for that, you
didn't even fucking know.
Yo! Can you
not swear so much?
Fuck that, you want
me to be a mute?
I'm sorry, dad.
For what?
For fighting with him.
You could've kicked his ass.
Of course.
He needs a proper beating.
Why?
He blames me for his life.
For your mom leaving, for
not getting into college,
that's why he settled as a barber.
He's just feeble-minded,
that's all.
You're wiser,
please understand him.
He's still a good kid,
be nice to him.
He's trying to make
something of his life.
Make up your mind,
whose side are you on?
Dad.
I heard your head's cloudy.
Me?
I hear you forget stuff.
Nope.
Over time, you won't remember me?
Good, you'll forget all
the troubles I caused.
- What are you doing?
- Hold still.
Even if you forget everything,
don't forget this.
I'm being a good son.
Don't forget it.
Get married.
That's how you become a good son.
So damn skinny...
Sir, how much is this?
$10, would you like one?
Am I late?
What are you doing?
Paying my respect.
What right do you have?!
Don't be like that, I was
almost his son-in-law.
Done? Go now.
Don't be so harsh, I'm
not even worth hating.
I'm leaving here.
I came to see you one last time.
You might not believe me,
but I wanted to apologize.
Fine, just go.
Have a good life.
- Want it?
- Hey, uncle.
Come here, come.
Isn't that white one hot?
Uncle, can you steal me one?
Kids nowadays
swap phones regularly!
Take a good look!
Only I have a dumbphone.
Everyone's got smartphones!
It's so embarrassing at school!
Ow, I bit my tongue!
Get! You little twat!
So fucking annoying!
Sir, please don't do that!
Honey, I'm done.
This isn't the place,
please leave.
Isn't the place?
Anything's possible.
Honey, be the better man.
This isn't a whorehouse, please go.
Motherfucker.
Say that again.
Please leave!
- Stay back!
- Honey!
Stay back!
I said we're not like
that, apologize to her.
Apologize? To a barber?!
Yeah! Yeah!
- What if I don't?
- Hey!
What if I don't want to?
- Motherfucker!
- You're nuts!
The fuck you're doing?!
Who the fuck are you?!
- Asshole!
- Fucker!
Fucking bastard!
You fucker! Fucker!
Motherfucker!
That the best you got?!
- Hello? Police?
- Come here, get up!
You come here!
Motherfucker!
Tae-il.
As your sister-in-law,
I have a favor.
Could you leave home?
There's no room,
and Song's growing up,
and I don't feel comfortable.
Honey, seriously!
Enough.
We got a shop to run.
Uncle!
What?
Dad says you should
go away for 3 days.
Mom'll cool down by then.
Here, it's from dad.
He said not to tell mom.
And this.
Here, from mom.
She knows you're broke.
She said not to
mention this to dad.
They got a communication problem.
7 year itch maybe?
Take it!
Bye.
Song.
Be good to your dad.
Only he can put up with our shit.
Whatever.
- Uncle!
- What?
We all knew that except you.
Bye.
Stop swearing.
Fuck you.
You're so much prettier in person.
See? I told you.
Please.
Sorry.
Got anything you wanna ask him?
Please feel free.
Sure.
It's been paid.
Your guardian already paid.
What?
Isn't Ms. JU Ho-jung your guardian?
He found out 2 years ago.
He never even got treated
in jail, that idiot.
Now you know...
His sentence was
suspended because of it,
he served half of his sentence,
and was declared terminally ill.
Who is it?
- Ms. HAN Song-ji?
- Yes, it's me.
Here you go.
- Good bye.
- Bye.
So fucking hot!
Holy fucking shit!
Fuck!
It was hard stealing
it, go to college
He did it!
Uncle!
I fucking love it!
Fine, let's see how good you are.
Bang! Bang!
Crash! What?!
What is that? Hit me!
Didn't I say I'll risk my
life for my innocence?
I'll prove it with death.
Moron, what are you saying?!
One hit will kill you, stay away!
Yes, priest, your body is...
Shut up!
Hurts?
So much.
Isn't it stuffy being here?
Of course, so stuffy here.
Wanna eat anything?
You.
Wanna do anything?
A walk, and a chat.
His chart.
I...
love you too.
Sir.
That bastard...
is making me bow to him now.
Dammit...
I knelt down...
Dad.
I actually almost got married.
But I messed it all up.
You know my life's a mess.
You know that Suhyup Bank?
She works there.
So pretty and a devoted daughter.
When her dad was sick,
she took care of him.
How can I ask her
to take care of me?
I wanted to give her the
money and disappear...
Even when I'm gone,
please be good to her.
She doesn't have a dad.
So you become her dad.
She's a girl your son really loves.
You hear me?
I'm sorry, father.
"On a cold day, I long for him...
He left this world, but he's
with me in my daily life."
I agree.
If you miss someone dearly,
while walking, eating
and even working,
your thoughts are filled
with the loved one.
They say time is the best medicine.
But I think those moments you
shared remain clear as time passes.
Have you also understood
your loved one,
only after some time has passed?
Here's our next song.
Requested by #0912,
'Memory, More Than Love'...